<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Menma’s Tera Guides on Tenacity</title>
    <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Menma’s Tera Guides on Tenacity</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1. Download</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/download/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/download/</guid>
      <description>Create an account:https://account.menmastera.com/register
Download link:https://menmastera.com/download</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. Introduction to basics</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Basic about the server Server is running on Patch - 100.2. As of writing this post, server are located in Starsbourg, France, EU. Server is set to PvP outside of safezone areas. But majority of PvP only happens in Velika Outskirts. Support for Menma&amp;rsquo;s TERA has been added to Shinra which you can find HERE Skill advancements are same as normal Tera, but you have one EP page &amp;amp; no cards</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3.1 Gearing - PvE</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/pve-gearing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/pve-gearing/</guid>
      <description>General Guide Massive thanks to Prince.Pluto for creating this document! You can find it HERE - General Guide to Menma&amp;amp;rsquo;s TERA Server
Gear You get the basic blue Azart gear to start with when you make your character.
You can get accessory crystals from vanguards credits, like in the original version. For Dark Light &amp;amp; Annihilation gear you should do dungeons such as Red Refuge &amp;amp; RK9, there you will get gear boxes (The gear options always random)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Class Crit Factors</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/class-crit-cap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/class-crit-cap/</guid>
      <description>A crit cap or crit-factor cap is the point at which having any more crit factor is a detriment to your DPS potential.
What Factors Influence the Crit Cap? Boss Level versus Your Level The difference between the target and your level will adjust how much crit factor is needed for your skills to crit.
It might be an impact on how much crit resist the boss has but the important part is the higher you are relative to the target, the lower amount of crit factor you need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3.2 Gearing - PvP</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/pvp-gearing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/pvp-gearing/</guid>
      <description>General Guide Massive thanks to Prince.Pluto for creating this document! You can find it HERE - General Guide to Menma&amp;amp;rsquo;s TERA Server
Gear You require FULL PVP GEAR
Since pve gear have debuffs on it for pvp :
(Reduced damage by 40% &amp;amp; Increased damage taken by 40%) You will instantly receive 1.000 eternal tokens to buy all you need, you don&amp;rsquo;t need to buy them after.
Through said tokens you can also buy special Radiant Jewelery which is not useable in dungeons and maxed Relic/Halidom Enchanting gear Through Eternal tokens which you get at the start when you create your character or through Bellicardum reputation merchant you can buy +9 Enchantment Scrolls for PvP Gear NOTE: Through those tokens you can also buy Lvl 5 Brooch and other max.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Civil Unrest</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/civil-unrest-menma/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/civil-unrest-menma/</guid>
      <description>Look HERE if youre looking for a broader overview of Civil Unrest.
Server operates in UTC timezone. Please keep it in mind and act accordingly. Main difference you will notice is that map is different. As of p2.0 Civil Unrest is being held on Colossal Ruins map.
You can also freely use Prime battle solution inside the area.
Towers can only be placed 100 meters apart from each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rally Quest</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/rally-quest-menma/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/rally-quest-menma/</guid>
      <description>Server operates in UTC timezone. Please keep it in mind and act accordingly. All Guilds can accept [Rally] Guild Quest as long as weekly Valderon Token limit has not been reached. Rally Quest can be completed regardless of the amount of contribution as long as a Guild Member has contributed.
Menma&amp;rsquo;s Tera changed Rally BAMs significantly with Patch 2.0. There are now PvP, PvE and General Rally BAMs - all giving their unique rewards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General - Bamarama</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/bamarama-menma/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/bamarama-menma/</guid>
      <description>The New Bamarama is available now on Menma&amp;rsquo;s TERA.
Head over to the Freeholds North of Chebika to participate. To begin, speak with one of the Bookies: Tayana, Teena, or Linu. First, open the “Bamarama Tickets” Menu and purchase a minimum of 5 Menma’s Coins.
After purchasing your Menma’s Coins, interact with a Bookie again and open the “Monster Wager” menu.
Select the monster you want, and bet as many Menma’s Coins as you’d like!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General - Dreamstorm</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/dreamstorm-menma/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/dreamstorm-menma/</guid>
      <description>Look HERE if youre looking for a broader overview of Dreamstorm.
Menma&amp;rsquo;s TERA Solo content which you can do once daily on each of your characters. Only requirement is to kill AT LEAST one mob to receive the reward for the character.
By completing the vanguard you will get 500 Tikat.
Depending on your ranking during the event, you will receive extra 500/400/300/200/100 Tikat. Remember that Dreamstorm is open 10minutes before, so you can pick up the quest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General - Field Bosses</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/field-bosses-menma/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/field-bosses-menma/</guid>
      <description>Field Boss Monsters are large monsters in open world. They usually respawn every 5 to 6 hours after they die and drop great loot!
On Menma&amp;rsquo;s TERA you can find many more World Bosses spawning around different areas! Get your party and claim the loot for yourself.
Spawn Rates Field Boss Monsters Ortan, Hazard, and Cerrus can spawn between 4hr 30min to 5hr 30min from their death.
Images of new bosses will come soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General - Mystery Merchants</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/mystery-merchant-menma/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/menma-guide/mystery-merchant-menma/</guid>
      <description>Mystery Merchant is an NPC that sells goods in exchange for special currency called Nexus Mystery Merchant Coin.
You can obtain Nexus Mystery Market Coins through Vanguard Boxes [PvE] or by Vanguard Rewards [Battlegrounds].
Mystery Merchants are changed significantly on Menma&amp;rsquo;s Tera.
They spawn only in main city regions - Velika, Allemantheia, Kaiator, Baldera and their outskirts. You can find a lot of useful items when you go hunt for them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
