<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Домашняя страница on Tenacity</title>
    <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Домашняя страница on Tenacity</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.1</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/patch-note/2022-07-08-p1.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/patch-note/2022-07-08-p1.1/</guid>
      <description>Долгожданный патч 1.1 наконец-то почти готов к релизу. С изменениями в PvE, PvP, контенте Открытого мира, балансировке классов и, конечно же, ввод 64-битного клиента.
Игровой Клиент Игровой клиент был обновлен до 64-разрядной версии, DirectX 11. Добавлены новые поддерживаемые языки игры: Немецкий, французский, русский. Подземелья &amp;amp; PvE изменения Следующие подземелья были закрыты:
Шпиль страха Святилище Велики (Сложно) Остров Мертвых (сложно) Хроноплоскость (Сложно) Мастерская Леандра (сложно) Омут Антароса (сложно) Ангар RK-9 Лагерь Повстанцев Катакомбы Велики Святилище Велики Список новых подземелий</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1. Download</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/menma-guide/download/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/menma-guide/download/</guid>
      <description>Create an account:https://account.menmastera.com/register
Download link:https://menmastera.com/download
Torrent file can be found on Menma’s Discord https://discord.gg/menmastera</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1. Прогрессия</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/achievements/progression/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/achievements/progression/</guid>
      <description>| Уровень | Различный |
Достижения прогресса получить очень легко, так как вы будете собирать их, повышая уровень до 70 уровня, а затем развивая свои навыки.
Уровень Название ** Класс** ** Описание** Уровень 10 Все Достигли уровня 10. 20-й уровень Все Достигли 20-го уровня. Уровень 30 Все Достигли 30-го уровня. 40-й уровень Все Достигли 40-го уровня. 50-й уровень Все Достигли 50-го уровня. Вы заработали дополнительное место в инвентаре. Мастер-лучник Archer Достигните 60-го уровня в качестве лучника.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. Proxy Mods</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/menma-guide/proxy-mods/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/menma-guide/proxy-mods/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2.1 Мировые боссы (Арун)</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/achievements/world-bosses-arun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/achievements/world-bosses-arun/</guid>
      <description>Локации и время появления совершенно случайны. В то время как у некоторых боссов есть только 1 возможная локация, у других есть более одного места, где они могут появляться. Отмеченное время появления - это общее время того, что было замечено в прошлом. Например, 6-24, это означает случайное время возрождения от 6 до 24 часов.
| South Arun
South Arun Arakia Время возрождения: 6-24 часа
Lanok Время возрождения: 6-24 часа
Barraq Время возрождения: 6-24 часа</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2.2 Мировые боссы (Шара)</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/achievements/world-bosses-shara/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/achievements/world-bosses-shara/</guid>
      <description>Отмеченное время появления - это общее время того, что было замечено в прошлом. Например, 6-24, это означает случайное время возрождения от 6 до 24 часов.
| South Shara | North Shara
South Shara Andras Время возрождения: 6-24 часа
Terkasia Время возрождения: 6-24 часа
Kestol Время возрождения: 6-24 часа
Teriak Время возрождения: 6-24 часа
Dulagoras Время возрождения: 6-24 часа
Nyxarras Время возрождения: 12-24+ часа
Huzrat Время возрождения: 12-24+ часа
Kelthuzad Время возрождения: 12-24+ часа</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3. Introduction to basics</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/menma-guide/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/menma-guide/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Basic about the server Server is running on old lvl70 Patch - 92.4 from March 2020 As of writing this post, server are located in Starsbourg, France, EU. Server is set to PvP As of writing this post,the client is 32-bit, and possible compatibility with a 64-bit client might come later. Support for Menma&amp;rsquo;s TERA has been added to Shinra which you can find HERE Skill advancements are same as normal Tera, but you have one EP page &amp;amp; no cards</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4.1 Gearing - PvP</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/menma-guide/pvp-gearing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/menma-guide/pvp-gearing/</guid>
      <description>Gear You require FULL PVP GEAR
Since pve gear have debuffs on it for pvp :
(Reduced damage by 40% &amp;amp; Increased damage taken by 40%) You will instantly receive 1.000 eternal tokens to buy all you need, you don&amp;rsquo;t need to buy them after.
Through said tokens you can also buy special Radiant Jewelery which is not useable in dungeons and maxed Relic/Halidom Enchanting gear Through Eternal tokens which you get at the start when you create your character or through Bellicardum reputation merchant you can buy +9 Enchantment Scrolls for PvP Gear NOTE: Through those tokens you can also buy Lvl 5 Brooch and other max.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PvP и дуэли</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/achievements/pvp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/achievements/pvp/</guid>
      <description>| Дуэли | Смертельные поединки | Поля сражений | Skills | Civil Unrest |
Достижения PvP отмечены на вкладке &amp;ldquo;Специальные&amp;rdquo; в меню достижений. Они не засчитываются в ваш выигрыш в целом, но завершение определенных действий может дать вам небольшой бафф.
Дуэли Дуэли можно просто начать, нажав на игрока и выбрав опцию &amp;ldquo;** Дуэль **&amp;rdquo;, которая спрашивает другого игрока, хочет ли он сразиться с вами.
Название Класс Описание Награда Соревновательный Всего Участвовал в 10 поединках.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Civil Unrest on Menma</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/menma-guide/civil-unrest-menma/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/menma-guide/civil-unrest-menma/</guid>
      <description>Look HERE if youre looking for a broader overview of Civil Unrest.
Server operates in UTC timezone. Please keep it in mind and act accordingly. Main difference you will notice is that map is different. As of p1.0.7 Civil Unrest is being held on destroyed Island of Dawn.
You can also freely use Prime battle solution inside the area.
Towers can only be placed 100 meters apart from each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guild vs Guild</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/menma-guide/guild-vs-guild/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/menma-guide/guild-vs-guild/</guid>
      <description>Guilds on Menma&amp;rsquo;s TERA are slightly different. Limit of players in one guild was set to 30 meters max; impossible to raise slots further.
Guild vs Guild Guilds can participate in Guild versus Guild (GvG) battles.
Once war is declared, for up to 24 hours, the competing guilds can attack and kill each other on sight anywhere except in Safe Zones. A guild can be involved in up to three such battles at one time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outlaw</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/menma-guide/outlaw-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/menma-guide/outlaw-system/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rally Quest</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/menma-guide/rally-quest-menma/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/menma-guide/rally-quest-menma/</guid>
      <description>Server operates in UTC timezone. Please keep it in mind and act accordingly. All Guilds can accept [Rally] Guild Quest as long as weekly Valderon Token limit has not been reached. Rally Quest can be completed regardless of the amount of contribution as long as a Guild Member has contributed.
Reward RANK BOX REWARD Rank 1 Rank 1 Reward Box 5 milion Bellicarium Reputation
2.000 Tikat Rank 2 Rank 2 Reward Box 1 milion Bellicarium Reputation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4.2 Gearing - PvE</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/menma-guide/pve-gearing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/menma-guide/pve-gearing/</guid>
      <description>Gear You get the basic blue Azart gear to start with when you make your character.
You can get accessory crystals from vanguards credits, like in the original version. For Dark Light &amp;amp; Annihilation gear you should do dungeons such as Red Refuge &amp;amp; RK9, there you will get gear boxes (The gear options always random)
Best you can get: 4x random roll on weapon (In addition to have double CRD) Except healers, their max rolls are 3xHow to get Kaia / Mythic Gear Mythic gear, also referred to as Kaia gear, is an available upgrade for gold Exodor gear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Class Crit Factors</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/menma-guide/class-crit-cap/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/ru/menma-guide/class-crit-cap/</guid>
      <description>A crit cap or crit-factor cap is the point at which having any more crit factor is a detriment to your DPS potential.
What Factors Influence the Crit Cap? Boss Level versus Your Level The difference between the target and your level will adjust how much crit factor is needed for your skills to crit.
It might be an impact on how much crit resist the boss has but the important part is the higher you are relative to the target, the lower amount of crit factor you need.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
