<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Notas de Parche Menma&#39;s TERA on Tenacidad</title>
    <link>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Notas de Parche Menma&#39;s TERA on Tenacidad</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.0.8</title>
      <link>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2022-06-02-p1.0.8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2022-06-02-p1.0.8/</guid>
      <description>Miscellaneous Maximum guild size has been increased to 35. All inactive accounts that did not log in since January 1st, 2022, have had their character names freed. Approximately 800 names have been freed. All Characters of level 70 have received 1x Eternal Gear Token Box on their Parcel Post. Fishing Rods have been temporarily disabled due to them being used to escape knockdown state with no cooldown. They will be fixed and brought back at a later patch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.0.7</title>
      <link>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2022-05-22-p1.0.7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2022-05-22-p1.0.7/</guid>
      <description>Golden Halidoms &amp;amp; Relics Manaya’s Core (Hard) Nightmare Shandra Manaya has a 20% chance to drop 1-2 Rank IV Halidoms or Relics alongside the Rank II ones that would already drop, the latter which now has a 50% chance to drop. Velik’s Sanctuary (Hard) Nightmare Lakan has a 50% chance to drop 1-3 Rank II Halidoms or Relics. Bahaar/Timescape/Forsaken Island 75% chance to drop 1-4 Rank I Halidoms or Relics. Partners Physical and Magical Amplification Superior Companions have been added to the Tikat Shop for 5,000 Tikats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.0.6</title>
      <link>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2022-05-15-p1.0.6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2022-05-15-p1.0.6/</guid>
      <description>Patch v1.0.6 brings various unique changes to the gear, PvP and miscellaneous gameplay improvements. Please find the details below.
TERA Club New item added: &amp;lt;Menma’s Multi-Nostrum&amp;gt; Upon use, applies Everful Nostrum, Strong Bravery, Superior Noctenium Elixir and Hot or Salty Fish Buffet buffs, the last one depending on your class. New Starting Item Eternal Gear Token Box has been added. Eternal Gear Token Box will replace existing Bellicarium Credits Item which new characters used to receive at the start of the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.0.5</title>
      <link>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2022-05-01-p1.0.5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2022-05-01-p1.0.5/</guid>
      <description>Some scheduled changes have been postponed for the next patch due to time limitations, and will be coming as soon as possible.
Battleground Fraywind Canyon no longer gives personal gear over item level 448. All Battlegrounds should stay up 24/7 now with no shutdown time. Removed faulty Civil Unrest NPC Teleport option (You would get doomzoned if you used it) Changed CU Rewards to: 1st Place: 5M Bellicarium Credit token 5k Tikat Tokens 2nd Place: 5M Bellicarium Credit Token 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.0.4</title>
      <link>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2021-09-13-p1.0.4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2021-09-13-p1.0.4/</guid>
      <description>Crafting Changed craft level requirements of Golden Darics &amp;amp; Silver Siglos to 1 point (Basic Crafting Level) Changed craft level requirements of Golden Plates &amp;amp; Silver Plates to 500 points (Artisan Crafting Level) Artisan level test of Smelting now requires Golden Daric crafting only to pass. Master level test of Smelting now requires Golden Plate crafting only to pass. Artisan level test of Processing now requires Silver Siglo crafting only to pass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.0.3</title>
      <link>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2021-09-08-p1.0.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2021-09-08-p1.0.3/</guid>
      <description>General Kaia’s Anvil quest required for unlocking the Kaia upgrade NPC is now automatically starting at level 70 (minimum item level required 461). You no longer have to do the exodor quest line to get it. The item Bellicarium Credits (5m) no longer expires after 1 hour of acquiring. Increased amount of maximum Adventure Coins to 2000 for non-TERA Club members and to 6000 for TERA Club members. The UI now properly displays Adventure Coins recharge rate of 20 for TERA Club members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.0.2</title>
      <link>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2021-08-30-p1.0.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2021-08-30-p1.0.2/</guid>
      <description>General Healers weapons should now drop unidentified. Non-healer weapons with no stats will drop identified now and will be missing the top selectable stat (enrage/cdr/attack speed/crit factor). Masks from Transcendent Mask Coupon shop require 1 coupon now instead of previous 6(?). Adjusted Battered Oath Gear sell price to 1,000 gold. Deleting a character over level 50 will now require 24 hours waiting time before being deleted. Replaced some of the non tradeable costumes with their tradeable versions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.0.1</title>
      <link>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2021-08-29-p1.0.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2021-08-29-p1.0.1/</guid>
      <description>General Skill Advancement gold cost has been reduced to 0. Tikat is now obtainable through vanguard initiative merchant on an exchange ratio of 1:1. Ancient Accessory Morpher merchant price has been changed to 1,000g compared to previous 10,000g. Skill Advancement scrolls have been added to the Bellicarium Credit Merchant shop at 10 credit per scroll. Adjusted price of Prime Battle Solution to 10 gold. Veteran title reward has been switched to the special glowing title called “Pride of Menma”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developer’s Note – September 2021</title>
      <link>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2021-09-01-dev-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2021-09-01-dev-note/</guid>
      <description>Instead of reposting Dev-Note here, you can find it at the official website:
Menma’s TERA Server</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.0 | The Release</title>
      <link>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2021-08-28-p1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2021-08-28-p1.0/</guid>
      <description>Menma’s TERA release is finally upon us, aiming to bring the game to as close to its glory days as possible. And now a word from our patch notes. Let’s goooo. Good luck to me writing the notes now.
Character Creation
On character creation you will be receiving Heroic Oath Gear, PvP crystals, Relic/Halidom I, accessories and a level 70 scroll. Adventure Coins
Maximum Adventure Coins for TERA Club accounts increased to 5000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 0.2</title>
      <link>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2021-06-29-p0.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2021-06-29-p0.2/</guid>
      <description>The First Class Balance Attempt General Added War Cry Chest to Tikat Shop. Guild Join Cooldown is now set to 0. Increased maximum amount of Bellicarium credits from 2m to 32m. (Maximum limit won’t show in client yet) Apex Scroll has been added to the Eternal Gear Token Shop. The Colosseum is now only solo queue. Added The Colosseum 3v3 (Team) premade queue. (Currently accessible from Champion’s Skyring Mark V (Team) option in Instance Matching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 0.1 | The Open Beta</title>
      <link>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2021-06-12-p0.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zerraa.github.io/tenacity-tera.eu/es/patch-note/2021-06-12-p0.1/</guid>
      <description>Menma’s TERA open beta testing is upon us, and comes with huge changes to the game we know as TERA. It’s time to make the switch!
Character Selection Screen
The Character Selection screen has been replaced with the old 2013 style character selection. Island of Dawn
The ruined Island of Dawn has been replaced with the old 2013 Island of Dawn. The Island of Dawn monsters of the areas in the bottom have been buffed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
