<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Patch Notes for Menma&#39;s TERA on Tenacity</title>
    <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Patch Notes for Menma&#39;s TERA on Tenacity</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.8.5 - Final Preparations</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-05-08-p1.8.5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-05-08-p1.8.5/</guid>
      <description>Battle Pass (Season II) You can now purchase PvE Hero Tokens from the PvP shop. Likewise, you can also purchase PvP Hero Tokens from the PvE shop. Bamarama (Round II) You must now place bets using at least five 100 Tikat Bags. You can purchase this item from the Tikat Store. No longer uses Bamarama Coins to place bets. Bamarama Coin NPCs have been temporarily removed. This is a limited time event, so participate as often as possible!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.8.3 - The Battle Rages!</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-04-07-p1.8.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-04-07-p1.8.3/</guid>
      <description>Adventurers, a new patch is coming!
We know many of you are interested in our upcoming big patch, which we teased briefly in Patch 1.8. The entire team is working hard to make it the best it can be, but we&amp;rsquo;re not ready to share more details yet. If you want to refresh your memory on what we&amp;rsquo;ve revealed this far, you can follow the previous link. We know you are eager to see what we have in store and to learn more about our plans, but we kindly ask for your patience until we&amp;rsquo;re happier with the state of the patch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.8.4 - PvP’s Fine-Tuned Fight</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-04-20-p1.8.4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-04-20-p1.8.4/</guid>
      <description>Adventurers, a new patch is coming!
PvE As for our upcoming content, we&amp;rsquo;ve been hard at work and hope to have more solid previews soon. As previously mentioned, this is our largest patch to date and we want to make it as good as we can; only showing previews when we can guarantee its quality. We understand that some of you may feel burnt out with our current content, but our stance on this for now is that we&amp;rsquo;d rather take our time to assure quality than to rush a poor product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 2.0.6 - R9 The Big One!</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-04-01-p2.0-69/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-04-01-p2.0-69/</guid>
      <description>Adventurers, a new patch is coming!
We are excited to announce that we have just released a massive patch for our beloved MMORPG. This patch contains so many changes that we can&amp;rsquo;t even list them all here. Seriously, it would take us hours to write down everything we have done to improve your gaming experience. Some of the changes are big, some are small, some are obvious, some are subtle, some are game-changing, some are cosmetic, some are bug fixes, some are new features, some are balance tweaks, some are quality of life improvements, some are surprises, some are secrets, and some are&amp;hellip; well, you&amp;rsquo;ll have to find out for yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.8.2 – Kaia&#39;s Conquest</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-03-29-p1.8.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-03-29-p1.8.2/</guid>
      <description>Adventurers, a new patch is coming!
Class Changes Brawler Growing Fury&amp;rsquo;s Irregular Optimization NEW: Increases damage from behind by 10% and overall damage by 69.7%. OLD: Increases damage from behind by 10% and overall damage by 73%. Design Note: This change will result in a 1.5% damage nerf when using Irregular Growing Fury.
Gunner [PvE] Fixed a bug which caused the class to deal much more damage than intended. Reaper Fixed a bug where Shadow Reaping could not be dispelled with Regression or Plague of Exhaustion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.8.1 – Hotfixes</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-03-25-p1.8.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-03-25-p1.8.1/</guid>
      <description>Adventurers, a new patch is coming!
Battle Pass: Season II Added Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Endless Fight (15v15) to [Battle Pass] Battleground Mission Ticket. Adjusted the Novice Dungeon Mission icons to help players to easily distinguish between Novice and Expert missions in their inventory. Combining [Battle Pass] Battleground Token with their respective mission now correctly gives Menma&amp;rsquo;s PvP Hero Fragments. Battleground Changes Leaderboard Achieving 1st, 2nd or 3rd place on the leaderboard now rewards a unique title!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.8 – Kaia’s Call to Battle</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-03-23-p1.8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-03-23-p1.8/</guid>
      <description>Adventurers, a new patch is coming!
Future Plans While this patch cycle and its dungeons are coming to a close, the entire team is hard at work on a big content patch. We promise that this upcoming patch is bigger and better than anything we&amp;rsquo;ve done before, and includes major changes for both PvE and PvP. Additionally, we even hope to include proper translations in full for French and German. The entire team is incredibly excited, and we can&amp;rsquo;t wait to share more information with you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.7.1-R2 – Hotfixes</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-03-05-p1.7.1-r2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-03-05-p1.7.1-r2/</guid>
      <description>Class Changes All Classes Slightly adjusted mount crit power passive system to better sync with the activation conditions added last patch. To see more information about the aforementioned activation system, click here. Brawler Growing Fury (Irregular) No longer reduces Endurance by 90. Increases damage taken by 50%. Mystic *Design Note: *Although we aren&amp;rsquo;t making Mystic changes with this patch, we&amp;rsquo;re keeping a very close eye on how it&amp;rsquo;s performing after our rework in 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.7.1 – PvE Adjustments</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-03-02-p1.7.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-03-02-p1.7.1/</guid>
      <description>PvP Overview We&amp;rsquo;re aware of and have been listening closely to the community&amp;rsquo;s concerns centered around the overall state of PvP balancing. As stated before, we&amp;rsquo;re going to be doing continual changes over a long period. Our immediate goal was to foster the community back to life to get games popping and make the content playable before sinking our teeth deep into balancing. We&amp;rsquo;re aware that our work has just begun, and we understand that we&amp;rsquo;re nowhere near ready to relax yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.7 - PvP Balancing</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-02-24-p1.7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-02-24-p1.7/</guid>
      <description>This time around, we&amp;rsquo;ve been focusing a lot of our time on PvP. We&amp;rsquo;ve snuck in some PvE changes here and there, but those interested in PvE should stay tuned for patches in the next couple of weeks.
Many of the changes are our first steps toward balancing many different aspects of PvP in Menma&amp;rsquo;s TERA. We continue to ask for your patience while we do so, as balancing every part of the game in one patch is not possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.6.2 - Second Part of Hotfixes</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-02-09-p1.6.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-02-09-p1.6.2/</guid>
      <description>Dungeon Changes Forbidden Arena (Undying Warlord) Fixed issue where lines still had a delay when targeting the healer and appearing. Class Changes Brawler Fixed an issue where Flying Kick gets body-blocked by party members. Battleground Changes Velocity Advancement on Priest and Mystic has been turned off and cannot be used inside of battlefields.
If you queue with this advancement turned on, you can turn it off inside or choose a different advancement before the fight starts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.6.1 – Hotfixes</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-02-08-p1.6.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-02-08-p1.6.1/</guid>
      <description>Dungeon Changes Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss (Hard) Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s orb mechanic now breaks Divine Protection and shatters Guardian Barrier, which leaves no chance of survival. This is what we intended from the start.
Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s debuffs now get cleared correctly.
The Plexus (Hard) Manaya&amp;rsquo;s debuffs now get cleared correctly. Battleground Changes Shore Hold (10v10) Now limits you to 1~2 tanks per team. Corsair&amp;rsquo;s Stronghold (15v15) &amp;amp; Shore Hold (10v10) A new aura has been added that replenishes 459 MP every 5 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.6 – PvP returns, PvE systematic changes, and more</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-02-06-p1.6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-02-06-p1.6/</guid>
      <description>There is a lot going on with this patch, so we&amp;rsquo;ll split this design note into two sections with bullet points. Hopefully this&amp;rsquo;ll help highlight what we believe are the most important changes for our players to see. This is the first time since we have joined the team that we&amp;rsquo;ve been making such large notable changes for both PvE and PvP simultaneously.
PvE We have received a lot of valuable feedback, with a common trend of feeling tired of our current lineup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.5 – Boss Partners, General Content, and more…</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-01-17-p1.5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2023-01-17-p1.5/</guid>
      <description>The last year has been a blast, and we as a team have come a long way from when we first started working on this project. We&amp;rsquo;ve learnt a ton, largely in part to your constructive feedback and efforts from the community. We&amp;rsquo;re now looking into taking things to the next level in the coming year. This small patch wraps up a number of events, and it also wraps up a few projects started in the previous year including changes to the Island of Dawn and the boss pet system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.4.2 – Holiday Adjustments</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-12-28-p1.4.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-12-28-p1.4.2/</guid>
      <description>Dungeon Adjustments The Plexus (Hard) Shandra Manaya has been reverted back to her normal size. RK-9 Kennel (Normal Mode) RK-9 will no longer aggro until attacked. All Dungeons Added Intelligence Report Left and Right parts in possible loot table
Replaced Essence of the Nexus II with Agaia Tokens
Added Sea of Honor maps in possible loot table
Added Naslow&amp;rsquo;s Treasure Map Left and Right parts in possible loot table
Adjusted loot of Hidden Wooden/Silver/Gold Crate from Naslow Treasure</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.4.1 – Hotfixes</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-12-18-p1.4.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-12-18-p1.4.1/</guid>
      <description>PVE Content Changes Events Fixed Wintera not awarding Wintera tokens. Wintera now awards 50 tokens via vanguard quest. Fixed Christmas Map Treasures to be party-wide rather than rolled for. Fat Santa loot updated. Dungeons The Plexus Decreased Nightmare Shandra Manaya&amp;rsquo;s HP from 50.6 billion to 47.5 billion. Changed Nightmare Shandra Manaya&amp;rsquo;s spawn location to the center of the room. Nightmare Shandra Manaya will not aggro until attacked. Fixed issue where Nightmare Shandra Manaya would not drop aggro if people were outside the arena.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.4 – Life Skilling, Class Revamps, PvE Redesign and Christmas</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-12-13-p1.4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-12-13-p1.4/</guid>
      <description>PVE Content Changes Design Note
A number of dungeons in the current PVE roster, ranging from entry-level dungeons to dungeons of the highest difficulty, have been reworked to not only bring boss HP values in-line with the balancing of classes that come with Patch 1.4, but should also make content that may previously have been a burden, more enjoyable to run. Naturally, these adjustments are subject to change, so we&amp;rsquo;ll be reviewing the state of content and learning from your feedback in the coming weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.3.1 – Battle Pass Adjustments &amp; General Hotfixes</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-11-15-p1.3.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-11-15-p1.3.1/</guid>
      <description>Menma’s Hunter Event (Battle Pass) After reviewing feedback from the community, we’ve decided to make some significant changes to the Battle Pass system. Alongside a wealth of quality of life improvements, the new Dungeon Mission Box now contains 2 new “Mission Tickets,” allowing players to select specific dungeons they’d like to run. Dungeons within the “Dungeon Group Mission” boxes have also been amended. We hope these changes make it slightly more enjoyable to complete your Battle Pass!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.3 – Finishing Accessories And Preparing For The Future</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-11-07-p1.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-11-07-p1.3/</guid>
      <description>Dungeon Changes New Dungeons The following dungeons have been added:
RK-9 Kennel – Item level 472. Dragon’s Lair (previously Commander’s Residence) – Item level 481. Demokron Factory (Hard) – Item level 485. Dragon’s Lair will be available twice per character per day on the weekends, and the vanguard will be claimable once daily on Saturday + Sunday. Notable rewards include: Refined Mana Essence, Agaia Material Tokens, 10K Item XP. The raid can be accessed via scrolls sold by the Specialty Merchant, or via instance matching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.2.1 – Jewellery And More…</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-10-11-p1.2.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-10-11-p1.2.1/</guid>
      <description>Dungeon Changes New Dungeons The following dungeons have been added:
Forbidden Arena [Undying Warlord] – Item level 480. Forbidden Arena [Nightmare Undying Warlord] – Item level 490. Rampaging RK-9 Kennel – Item level 490. Dungeons can be accessed via the Vanguard menu or from teleport scrolls in the Specialty Store.
Unique rewards covered in the gear section below.
Dungeon Adjustments Ghilleglade: Added Dragonwing Scales and Item XP +10% to the drop table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.2 - New Dungeons &amp; Jewelry</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-09-27-p1.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-09-27-p1.2/</guid>
      <description>Dungeon Changes The following dungeons have been added:
Akalath Quarantine – Item level 475. Draakon Arena – Item level 480. Draakon Arena (Hard) – Item level 490. Dungeons can be accessed via the Vanguard menu or from teleport scrolls in the Specialty Store (Verrak Fortress Teleport Scroll + Draakon Arena Teleport Scroll). Entry to Draakon Arena must be unlocked by completing the quest &amp;lt;[Important] The Azart Commander&amp;gt;. Quest start is located outside of the dungeon entrance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.1.5 - The Festival of the Sun</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-08-30-p1.1.5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-08-30-p1.1.5/</guid>
      <description>Festival of the Sun The well known festival of the sun event is coming a little late in the game and will be remaining active from 1.1.5 maintenance until the end of September. Daily questing to earn Seashell Tokens that can be used in the Shurimon NPC located in Highwatch. Rewards are as follows: Battlegrounds Elin Event Duration: 7 Days (30th August 2022 after maintenance – 6th September 2022 23:59:59 UTC) Shore Hold Play 5 Games for Exodor Laundry Basket x3 Play 10 Games for 3,000 Tikat Play 15 Games for Dragon Skill: Mighty Solarian Wyvern (7 Days) Corsairs’ Stronghold Play 5 Games for Kaia’s Gear Box x5 Play 8 Games for 5,000 Tikat Play 10 Games for Exodor Laundry Basket x5 Play 20 Games for Liberation Scroll Champions’ Skyring Play 5 Games for 10 Diamonds Play 10 Games for 3,000 Tikat Play 15 Games for Dragon Skill: Mighty Solarian Wyvern (7 Days) Battleground Changes Equalised Gear: We added new equalised gear for battlegrounds provide a more balanced experience inside the battlegrounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.1.4 &#43; New PvE Community Managers Notes</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-08-20-p1.1.4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-08-20-p1.1.4/</guid>
      <description>General/Miscellaneous changes Disabled GvGs inside the city of Highwatch Enabled GvGs in the Velika region + inner city. Decreased cooldown of Strong Canephora Potion to 5 seconds. Decreased cooldown of Tempestuous Savage Draught to 5 minutes. Decreased cooldown of Inexorable Savage Draught to 5 minutes. Strong Canephora Potion is now overwritable by itself. Menma’s Multi-Nostrum will now give the Crit Factor Fish Buffet (Spicy) Instead of the Endurance Fish Buffet (Salty).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.1.3 - Hotfixes (Part 2B)</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-08-09-p1.1.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-08-09-p1.1.3/</guid>
      <description>New Elin Event An account based Elin Event has been added. It will last from 9/8/2022 till 15/8/2022. Participate in the following activities in order to receive additional rewards during the event period:
PvE Events Clear Bahaar’s Sanctum 5 Times = 25 Diamonds 15 Times = 50 Diamonds 25 Times = 10.000 Tikat Clear Forbidden Arena [Hagufna] 5 times = 500 Tikat 15 times = 1.000 Tikat 25 times = 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.1.1 - Hotfixes (Part 1)</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-07-12-p1.1.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-07-12-p1.1.1/</guid>
      <description>On this maintenance, a part of scheduled hotfixes have been added. More hotfixes will be coming in the following days.
General Reverted Reaper Starting Area to Ashen Hope. Character deleting timer is now normally set to 24 hours over level 50. Updated some skill tooltips to more accurately display skill descriptions. Stepstone Island quest that required the use of Bravery Potion, now requires Strong Bravery Potion instead, to avoid issues with Menma’s Multi Nostrum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.1.2 - Hotfixes (Part 2a)</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-08-01-p1.1.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-08-01-p1.1.2/</guid>
      <description>This week’s maintenance will come in 2 parts. First, this small part with some adjustments/fixes. Second will be coming towards the end of this week or next week’s Monday.
General Dressing Room has finally been fixed and is now the recommended way of picking up and buying costumes. Increased all Keen IV Etchings Crit Factor from 22 to 24. Added the following items to the Elleon’s Mark of Valor Shop: Federation Supply: Rejuvenation Potion for 10 Elleon’s Marks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.1</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-07-08-p1.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-07-08-p1.1/</guid>
      <description>The long awaited 1.1 patch is finally here. With changes to PvE, PvP, Open World content, Class Balancing and of course, the 64-bit client.
Game Client The game client has been updated to 64-bit, DirectX 11. Added new supported game languages: German, French, Russian. Dungeons &amp;amp; PvE The following dungeons are closing their doors:
Dreadspire Velik’s Sanctuary (Hard) Forsaken Island (Hard) Timescape (Hard) Grotto of Lost Souls (Hard) Antaroth’s Abyss (Hard) RK-9 Kennel Red Refuge Velik’s Hold Velik’s Sanctuary The new dungeon list is as follows:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.0.9</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-06-10-p1.0.9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-06-10-p1.0.9/</guid>
      <description>Guild Changes Increased Guild XP Rewards from Guild Quests by 10x. Decreased amount of Guild XP required for each Guild Level by 20%. Increased maximum amount of Valderon Tokens from 900 to 1500. Miscellaneous Disabled Pit of Petrax Leaderboards. Added Strong Canephora Potion to Elleon’s Mark of Valor for 5 Elleon’s Marks. Added Moongourd Pie to Eleon’s Mark of Valor for 10 Eleon’s Marks. Increased channels of all open world zones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.0.8</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-06-02-p1.0.8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-06-02-p1.0.8/</guid>
      <description>Miscellaneous Maximum guild size has been increased to 35. All inactive accounts that did not log in since January 1st, 2022, have had their character names freed. Approximately 800 names have been freed. All Characters of level 70 have received 1x Eternal Gear Token Box on their Parcel Post. Fishing Rods have been temporarily disabled due to them being used to escape knockdown state with no cooldown. They will be fixed and brought back at a later patch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.0.7</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-05-22-p1.0.7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-05-22-p1.0.7/</guid>
      <description>Golden Halidoms &amp;amp; Relics Manaya’s Core (Hard) Nightmare Shandra Manaya has a 20% chance to drop 1-2 Rank IV Halidoms or Relics alongside the Rank II ones that would already drop, the latter which now has a 50% chance to drop. Velik’s Sanctuary (Hard) Nightmare Lakan has a 50% chance to drop 1-3 Rank II Halidoms or Relics. Bahaar/Timescape/Forsaken Island 75% chance to drop 1-4 Rank I Halidoms or Relics. Partners Physical and Magical Amplification Superior Companions have been added to the Tikat Shop for 5,000 Tikats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.0.6</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-05-15-p1.0.6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-05-15-p1.0.6/</guid>
      <description>Patch v1.0.6 brings various unique changes to the gear, PvP and miscellaneous gameplay improvements. Please find the details below.
TERA Club New item added: &amp;lt;Menma’s Multi-Nostrum&amp;gt; Upon use, applies Everful Nostrum, Strong Bravery, Superior Noctenium Elixir and Hot or Salty Fish Buffet buffs, the last one depending on your class. New Starting Item Eternal Gear Token Box has been added. Eternal Gear Token Box will replace existing Bellicarium Credits Item which new characters used to receive at the start of the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.0.5</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-05-01-p1.0.5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2022-05-01-p1.0.5/</guid>
      <description>Some scheduled changes have been postponed for the next patch due to time limitations, and will be coming as soon as possible.
Battleground Fraywind Canyon no longer gives personal gear over item level 448. All Battlegrounds should stay up 24/7 now with no shutdown time. Removed faulty Civil Unrest NPC Teleport option (You would get doomzoned if you used it) Changed CU Rewards to: 1st Place: 5M Bellicarium Credit token 5k Tikat Tokens 2nd Place: 5M Bellicarium Credit Token 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.0.4</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2021-09-13-p1.0.4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2021-09-13-p1.0.4/</guid>
      <description>Crafting Changed craft level requirements of Golden Darics &amp;amp; Silver Siglos to 1 point (Basic Crafting Level) Changed craft level requirements of Golden Plates &amp;amp; Silver Plates to 500 points (Artisan Crafting Level) Artisan level test of Smelting now requires Golden Daric crafting only to pass. Master level test of Smelting now requires Golden Plate crafting only to pass. Artisan level test of Processing now requires Silver Siglo crafting only to pass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.0.3</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2021-09-08-p1.0.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2021-09-08-p1.0.3/</guid>
      <description>General Kaia’s Anvil quest required for unlocking the Kaia upgrade NPC is now automatically starting at level 70 (minimum item level required 461). You no longer have to do the exodor quest line to get it. The item Bellicarium Credits (5m) no longer expires after 1 hour of acquiring. Increased amount of maximum Adventure Coins to 2000 for non-TERA Club members and to 6000 for TERA Club members. The UI now properly displays Adventure Coins recharge rate of 20 for TERA Club members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.0.2</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2021-08-30-p1.0.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2021-08-30-p1.0.2/</guid>
      <description>General Healers weapons should now drop unidentified. Non-healer weapons with no stats will drop identified now and will be missing the top selectable stat (enrage/cdr/attack speed/crit factor). Masks from Transcendent Mask Coupon shop require 1 coupon now instead of previous 6(?). Adjusted Battered Oath Gear sell price to 1,000 gold. Deleting a character over level 50 will now require 24 hours waiting time before being deleted. Replaced some of the non tradeable costumes with their tradeable versions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.0.1</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2021-08-29-p1.0.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2021-08-29-p1.0.1/</guid>
      <description>General Skill Advancement gold cost has been reduced to 0. Tikat is now obtainable through vanguard initiative merchant on an exchange ratio of 1:1. Ancient Accessory Morpher merchant price has been changed to 1,000g compared to previous 10,000g. Skill Advancement scrolls have been added to the Bellicarium Credit Merchant shop at 10 credit per scroll. Adjusted price of Prime Battle Solution to 10 gold. Veteran title reward has been switched to the special glowing title called “Pride of Menma”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developer’s Note – September 2021</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2021-09-01-dev-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2021-09-01-dev-note/</guid>
      <description>Instead of reposting Dev-Note here, you can find it at the official website:
Menma’s TERA Server</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.0 | The Release</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2021-08-28-p1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2021-08-28-p1.0/</guid>
      <description>Menma’s TERA release is finally upon us, aiming to bring the game to as close to its glory days as possible. And now a word from our patch notes. Let’s goooo. Good luck to me writing the notes now.
Character Creation
On character creation you will be receiving Heroic Oath Gear, PvP crystals, Relic/Halidom I, accessories and a level 70 scroll. Adventure Coins
Maximum Adventure Coins for TERA Club accounts increased to 5000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 0.2</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2021-06-29-p0.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2021-06-29-p0.2/</guid>
      <description>The First Class Balance Attempt General Added War Cry Chest to Tikat Shop. Guild Join Cooldown is now set to 0. Increased maximum amount of Bellicarium credits from 2m to 32m. (Maximum limit won’t show in client yet) Apex Scroll has been added to the Eternal Gear Token Shop. The Colosseum is now only solo queue. Added The Colosseum 3v3 (Team) premade queue. (Currently accessible from Champion’s Skyring Mark V (Team) option in Instance Matching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 0.1 | The Open Beta</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2021-06-12-p0.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/en/patch-note/2021-06-12-p0.1/</guid>
      <description>Menma’s TERA open beta testing is upon us, and comes with huge changes to the game we know as TERA. It’s time to make the switch!
Character Selection Screen
The Character Selection screen has been replaced with the old 2013 style character selection. Island of Dawn
The ruined Island of Dawn has been replaced with the old 2013 Island of Dawn. The Island of Dawn monsters of the areas in the bottom have been buffed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
