<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Currently on MT: The Dream on </title>
    <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Currently on MT: The Dream on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Antaroth Abyss (Hard)</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/antaroth-abyss-hard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/antaroth-abyss-hard/</guid>
      <description>First Boss: Ghergof #Key Mechanics #Ice Puddle - The boss will target one of the players with a growing red circle, once it fills it will put down an Ice patch which will be used to avoid the mechanic below.
It is important to place this away from the boss, but not far because you’re going to need it for the “Delete This” mechanic. Delete This - A text message will show up saying :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Reach Citadel</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/dark-reach-citadel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/dark-reach-citadel/</guid>
      <description>First Boss: Theropath #Key Mechanics #Pull AoE - The boss will pull everyone towards him and then put an iframeable AoE on everyone, to survive this people need to spread so that the AoE does not overlap.
They do 50% HP damage in Normal Mode and 75% in Hard Mode. If you hit the boss with an AoE in hard mode the gauge will add 30 to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kalivan&#39;s Dreadnaught</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/kalivan-dreadnaught/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/kalivan-dreadnaught/</guid>
      <description>First Boss: Pepero #Key Mechanics #Protect the Kegs! - Throughout the fight, mobs will spawn:
“Suicide Soldiers are targeting the X!
Break an oak barrel and use Inferno Spores to take them out“Players will have to prevent these mobs from destroying the different Piles (Wine Barrels, Bomb Piles, Gunpowder Boxes, or Oil Barrels) in each corner of the arena. If any Pile is destroyed a message appears:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lilith&#39;s Keep (Hard)</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/lilith-keep-hard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/lilith-keep-hard/</guid>
      <description>First Boss: Pyrepelt #Key Mechanics #Leap - Shortly after you see this message:
“How annoying… I will kill you all!!“Pyrepelt will leap into the air. Upon impact, the entire area except for a narrow strip will be covered in a raging fire.
Fire Curtain - Message appears at certain intervals once Pyrepelt has lost sufficient health, and is followed by a series of multiple attacks:
“The flame will swallow you whole!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manaya Core (Hard)</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/manaya-core-hard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/manaya-core-hard/</guid>
      <description>First Boss: Hrathgol #MT: The Dream Changes: He gained 20% attack speed buff. Timer reduced to 3:30 minutes. Key Mechanics #Hrathgol now has a 6 minute enrage timer; in other words, if you don&amp;rsquo;t kill him within 6 minutes he&amp;rsquo;ll flip his feces and one-shot you all.
When Hrathgol&amp;rsquo;s health reaches 80%, 60%, 40%, and 20%, the boss mechanic will come into play.
Debuffs - A message will appear in the center of your screen that saying</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Refuge (Hard)</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/red-refuge-hard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/red-refuge-hard/</guid>
      <description>First Boss: Kalavese #Tank in the middle of the room to make the run a lot more smooth to deal with a Key Mechanic mentioned later.
Key Mechanics #Spinning In-Out - Cannot be blocked and iframed. A text indicator will show up saying:
“I’ll burn you to ashes”The boss stars spinning and will either attack in an inner donut or an outer donut first, followed by the other one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shadow Sanguinary (Hard)</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/shadow-sanguinary-hard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/shadow-sanguinary-hard/</guid>
      <description>First Boss: Pahoegar #For tanks in Hard Mode he hits a lot tougher when he&amp;rsquo;s not enraged where it may bleed through your block. Using Infuriate at the start of the fight is a good idea where it won&amp;rsquo;t bleed through block.
Key Mechanics #Pillars - Message shown on the center of your screen.
&amp;ldquo;Pahoegar is gathering power.&amp;rdquo;This mechanic will begin when the boss reaches 94% HP and then repeats about every 50-60 seconds (Normal Mode) from now on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timescape (Hard)</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/timescape-hard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/timescape-hard/</guid>
      <description>Timespheres #Ball 3 will be shieldless and the other two will be protected with a reflective shield. Dealing damage to a shielded sphere will deal damage to the player equal to 10% of his maximum HP.
High DPS parties should kill the shielded balls (1+2)
Then destroy the remaining ball (3).First Boss: Hemera #Key Mechanics #Your tank must bring the boss one of the spheres around the room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Velik&#39;s Sanctuary (Hard)</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/velik-sanctuary-hard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/velik-sanctuary-hard/</guid>
      <description>First Boss: Revived Darkan #Key Mechanics #Mana Generators - When the ring of fire appears, you will also notice the Lesser Magic Generators. However, if Darkan’s HP falls below 50%, the Lesser Generators will be replaced by Greater Generators and Ring of Fire will reset. Annihilation - Break the pylons with this attack so that it creates a safe zone for next attack.
Above 50% HP – Prepare to suffer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Velik’s Hold (Hard)</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/velik-hold-hard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/mt/velik-hold-hard/</guid>
      <description>First Boss: Kavador #Key Mechanics #Nightmare Roly Poly - He will randomly target a party member and roll in straight path and a message will appear:
“Doom!”He will do this 3 times. Then, he will bury underground and pop up near the person with aggro. This attack is instant death. Basic attacks #Right/Left Scratch - Attacks the person with aggro. Nothing special.
Fury Swipes - hit attack.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
