<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Patch Notes on </title>
    <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Patch Notes on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.8.5 - Final Preparations</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/2023-05-08-p1.8.5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/2023-05-08-p1.8.5/</guid>
      <description>Battle Pass (Season II) #You can now purchase PvE Hero Tokens from the PvP shop. Likewise, you can also purchase PvP Hero Tokens from the PvE shop. Bamarama (Round II) #You must now place bets using at least five 100 Tikat Bags. You can purchase this item from the Tikat Store. No longer uses Bamarama Coins to place bets. Bamarama Coin NPCs have been temporarily removed. This is a limited time event, so participate as often as possible!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.8.4 - A Fine-Tuned Fight</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/2023-04-20-p1.8.4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/2023-04-20-p1.8.4/</guid>
      <description>Adventurers, a new patch is coming!
PvE #As for our upcoming content, we&amp;rsquo;ve been hard at work and hope to have more solid previews soon. As previously mentioned, this is our largest patch to date and we want to make it as good as we can; only showing previews when we can guarantee its quality. We understand that some of you may feel burnt out with our current content, but our stance on this for now is that we&amp;rsquo;d rather take our time to assure quality than to rush a poor product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.8.3 - The Battle Rages!</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/2023-04-07-p1.8.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/2023-04-07-p1.8.3/</guid>
      <description>Adventurers, a new patch is coming!
We know many of you are interested in our upcoming big patch, which we teased briefly in Patch 1.8. The entire team is working hard to make it the best it can be, but we&amp;rsquo;re not ready to share more details yet. If you want to refresh your memory on what we&amp;rsquo;ve revealed this far, you can follow the previous link. We know you are eager to see what we have in store and to learn more about our plans, but we kindly ask for your patience until we&amp;rsquo;re happier with the state of the patch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 2.0.6 - R9 The Big One!</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/2023-04-01-p2.0-69/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/2023-04-01-p2.0-69/</guid>
      <description>Adventurers, a new patch is coming!
We are excited to announce that we have just released a massive patch for our beloved MMORPG. This patch contains so many changes that we can&amp;rsquo;t even list them all here. Seriously, it would take us hours to write down everything we have done to improve your gaming experience. Some of the changes are big, some are small, some are obvious, some are subtle, some are game-changing, some are cosmetic, some are bug fixes, some are new features, some are balance tweaks, some are quality of life improvements, some are surprises, some are secrets, and some are&amp;hellip; well, you&amp;rsquo;ll have to find out for yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.8.2 – Kaia&#39;s Conquest</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/2023-03-29-p1.8.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/2023-03-29-p1.8.2/</guid>
      <description>Adventurers, a new patch is coming!
Class Changes #Brawler #Growing Fury&amp;rsquo;s Irregular Optimization NEW: Increases damage from behind by 10% and overall damage by 69.7%. OLD: Increases damage from behind by 10% and overall damage by 73%. Design Note: This change will result in a 1.5% damage nerf when using Irregular Growing Fury.Gunner #[PvE] Fixed a bug which caused the class to deal much more damage than intended.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.8.1 – Hotfixes</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/2023-03-25-p1.8.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/2023-03-25-p1.8.1/</guid>
      <description>Adventurers, a new patch is coming!
Battle Pass: Season II #Added Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Endless Fight (15v15) to [Battle Pass] Battleground Mission Ticket. Adjusted the Novice Dungeon Mission icons to help players to easily distinguish between Novice and Expert missions in their inventory. Combining [Battle Pass] Battleground Token with their respective mission now correctly gives Menma&amp;rsquo;s PvP Hero Fragments. Battleground Changes #Leaderboard #Achieving 1st, 2nd or 3rd place on the leaderboard now rewards a unique title!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.8 – Kaia’s Call to Battles</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/2023-03-23-p1.8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/2023-03-23-p1.8/</guid>
      <description>Adventurers, a new patch is coming!
Future Plans #While this patch cycle and its dungeons are coming to a close, the entire team is hard at work on a big content patch. We promise that this upcoming patch is bigger and better than anything we&amp;rsquo;ve done before, and includes major changes for both PvE and PvP. Additionally, we even hope to include proper translations in full for French and German.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.7.1-R2 – Hotfixes</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/2023-03-05-p1.7.1-r2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/2023-03-05-p1.7.1-r2/</guid>
      <description>Class Changes #All Classes #Slightly adjusted mount crit power passive system to better sync with the activation conditions added last patch. To see more information about the aforementioned activation system, click here. Brawler #Growing Fury (Irregular) No longer reduces Endurance by 90. Increases damage taken by 50%. Mystic #*Design Note: *Although we aren&amp;rsquo;t making Mystic changes with this patch, we&amp;rsquo;re keeping a very close eye on how it&amp;rsquo;s performing after our rework in 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.7.1 – PvE Adjustments</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/2023-03-02-p1.7.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/2023-03-02-p1.7.1/</guid>
      <description>PvP Overview #We&amp;rsquo;re aware of and have been listening closely to the community&amp;rsquo;s concerns centered around the overall state of PvP balancing. As stated before, we&amp;rsquo;re going to be doing continual changes over a long period. Our immediate goal was to foster the community back to life to get games popping and make the content playable before sinking our teeth deep into balancing. We&amp;rsquo;re aware that our work has just begun, and we understand that we&amp;rsquo;re nowhere near ready to relax yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menma’s TERA 1.7 - PvP Balancing</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/2023-02-24-p1.7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/patch-notes/2023-02-24-p1.7/</guid>
      <description>This time around, we&amp;rsquo;ve been focusing a lot of our time on PvP. We&amp;rsquo;ve snuck in some PvE changes here and there, but those interested in PvE should stay tuned for patches in the next couple of weeks.
Many of the changes are our first steps toward balancing many different aspects of PvP in Menma&amp;rsquo;s TERA. We continue to ask for your patience while we do so, as balancing every part of the game in one patch is not possible.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
