<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dungeons on </title>
    <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dungeons on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Abscess</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/abscess/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/abscess/</guid>
      <description>PreFight #Just few mobs on the way when you enter the pathway to the first mobs. Nothing special, kill them and move to the first boss.
First Boss: Thalweg #Basic attacks #Slap - Simple two hit attack.
Slam - Simple two hit attack.
Random Target Laser - Basically, a random target will get the purple secondary aggro circle, the boss will turn to face him, and then he will shoot a beam of laser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Akalath Quarantine</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/akalath-quarantine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/akalath-quarantine/</guid>
      <description>First Boss: Akalath Travan #Key Mechanics #Color Mechanic - This mechanic is the same as in Ruinous Manor (Hard), oneshotting you if you fail or your debuff times out.
Mechanic starts when the boss says :
Bear my curse!And draws his swords away from his body.
Whenever he uses this mechanic, it will create a pulse of energy debuff on the players. Changing or giving them a new color if they have none.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Akeron&#39;s Inferno (Hard)</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/akeron-inferno/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/akeron-inferno/</guid>
      <description>First Boss: Darumag #Basic attacks #Claw - Darumag will attack frequently uses his claws. Claw attacks can be frontal, or to the side. He can even swipe from above.
All players hit will receive a Bleeding Effect. Darumag can also stomp (slamming the ground with both claws) or leap (jumping at a player and causing damage). Both attacks will apply a Bleeding Effect. Special attacks #Battle Cry - Darumag’s eyes will flash red and will deal deadly damage in form a shockwave from his chest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argon Corpus (Hard)</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/argon-corpus-hard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/argon-corpus-hard/</guid>
      <description>First Boss: Cygnus #Nothing too special on this boss.
The attack patterns are easy to learn and it does not have any 1 hit kill moves.
One notable attack is a poison trap attack that leaves a puddle of poison on the ground. When the mob HP is above 40%, the poison floor attack is usually targeted at a ranged DD or the healer. Below 40%, it will spam it on everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bahaar&#39;s Sanctum</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/bahaar-sanctum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/bahaar-sanctum/</guid>
      <description>The dungeon is broken up into two phases with the 2nd phase starting when you get Bahaar down to 20% health. You get loot after the first phase and you may even see LFGs for &amp;ldquo;Bahaar Farm P1&amp;rdquo; for this purpose, though probably less so now.
Finding videos of P1 is a bit tricky since most people who regularly clear P2 would consider P1 kinda pointless.
The key to understanding Bahaar is to look at his hammer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bathysmal Rise (Hard)</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/bathysmal-rise-hard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/bathysmal-rise-hard/</guid>
      <description>First Boss: Mephisis #The tank should aggro the boss towards the rock near the exit of the platform. You will be pushed a lot. Key Mechanics #Poisonous Gas - At 80% HP, you will receive a warning :
“The air’s too fresh. Let’s fix that!”That means the rocks will shatter in set timed interval.There are 2 rocks, on either side of the northern wall.
The second one will be announced by “There’s no antidote for my fury!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broken Prison</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/broken-prison/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/broken-prison/</guid>
      <description>Pre-Boss Battle #The first room has 6 Archdevan mobs.
They’re are just as same as Archdevan mobs you’ve encountered in Shadow Sanguinary and Lilith’s Keep. Defeat them and Balbatos will make his first appearance. After fighting him for 10% of his HP, he will summon Gorgoth and run away. First Boss: Gorgoth #Basic attacks #Basic Attack (Primary Aggro) – Strikes the person with Aggro twice with its snake arms and delivers a third blow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Channelworks</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/channelworks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/channelworks/</guid>
      <description>First Boss: Sentry AA-24 #This first boss is a stationary boss which deals damage by lasers which are ejected in front and behind of the boss. The boss can rotate however.
Special attacks #There is a mechanic at 75%, 50% and 25% where walls will spawn Message:
Initializing Trap Mode.You must get out of the middle and behind either side of walls as the boss will spawn ghost forms of previous bosses who will deal damage to anyone in the middle section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corrupted Skynest (Hard)</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/corrupted-skynest-hard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/corrupted-skynest-hard/</guid>
      <description>Pre-Boss BattleThere are some mobs in front of the gate. Simply kill them, no need to waste big skills on them.
Before the start of the fight, you should already be familiar with all following debuffs:
Standard debuff, if you dont take any other debuff before this one expires you will die.Fire debuffIce debuffVery Similar to Dreadspire, a bar exists that starts at 50 and will either tick up or down based on the debuffs the group has in total.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demokron Factory (Hard)</title>
      <link>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/demokron-factory-hard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tenacity-tera.eu/dungeons/dungeon/demokron-factory-hard/</guid>
      <description>First Boss: Vera &amp;amp; Prima #Vera is an Archdevan Lancer and Prima is an Archdevan Sorcerer. Players only need to take care of one of the two, usually the Lancer.
The other will disappear if one of them dies.
Prima can be CC’d (Stun, Sleep, Fear, etc). Let a DPS pull the Sorcerer away in the beginning and put CC on her with classes with lots of CC like Warrior, Berserker, Healers, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
